# **MD. Foisal Ahmed**



#### **Contact**

**Address:** 

House: 32 Road: 4, Nikunja-2,

Khilkhet, Dhaka-1229

Phone:

01763643663 01738244627

**Email:** 

foisal.cse@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fois al-ahmed-a67723169/

#### GitHub:

https://www.github.com/Foishaal Ahmed

#### Languages:

Bangla English

## **Summary**

About 3 years experienced with strong analytical skills and deep expertise in PHP(Laravel). An excellent problem-solver, able to quickly grasp complex systems and identify opportunities for improvements and resolution of critical issues. Precise in documentation, successfully documented processes, workflows, procedures.

### **Experience**

**Software Engineer (PHP, Laravel)** - 02/2022 to Present <u>Techvillage</u>, Dhaka

Web Developer (PHP, Laravel) - 10/2020 to 01/2022 ICTBANGLABD, DHAKA

**Web Developer (PHP, Codelgniter)** - 10/2019 to 04/2020 HRSOFTBD, DHAKA

### **Education**

BSC: **Computer Science & Engineering** - 2014 To 2018 Daffodil International University, Dhaka with CGPA 3.38 out of 4.00.

HSC: **Science** - 2010 To 2012 Rajshahi Collegiate School & College, Rajshahi with GPA 4.50 out of 5.00.

SSC: **Science** - 2008 To 2010 Mirjapur High School, Rajshahi with GPA 4.94 out of 5.00.

### Skills

Programming Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, PHP OOP, CSS,

SQL, MySQL.

PHP Framework: Laravel, Codelgniter.

JavaScript Framework & Library: jQuery, Vue, AJAX. Version Control: Git, GitHub, Sourcetree, Bitbucket

Web Server: cPanel, Linux (Digital Ocean).

# **Projects**

Name: PayMoney - Secure Online Payment Gateway

**Description**: PayMoney is an online payment gateway system

Technology: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, jQuery, AJAX.

Link: PayMoney

Name: Cornerstone

**Description**: Insurance policy website with policy management

svstem.

Technology: PHP, Codelgniter, MySQL, jQuery, AJAX.

Link: Cornerstone